remember for bumping mics I said I was
going to bring in some hats for you guys
yeah hell yeah hear some yeah dude
so funny Jeff R very limited amount this
for Christine this for you Dan I'm sorry
but I have shirts too so maybe you guys
want some you know I can't fit that
hat I I have fetal alcohol syndrome
which means that hat does not fit my
head put it on the last hook this will
be the best God damn it this always
happens to me in my life and it's always
embarrassing ridiculous feel horrible no
now I have to do in front of David H
this sucks no it's good put on the very
last
one oh you're right oh God damn it it
doesn't even the last one did it break
open yeah your head split open the last
hook Man black Lou really got a kick out
of that so that would be I try to
go now snap it Jesus man yeah but if
this was Shark Tank that would be your
thing now I go now here's a head a hat
for people with fetal alcohol
syndrome
did you guys watch a lot of TV I see you
both as more Sports oriented like hey
let's go out and throw the ball around
no we didn't have Dad's I did that too I
well I did that with my friends right
same as you as I got older no when I was
a kid it was very TV so I watched a lot
of TV shows that people my age are not
that aware of and Christine Knows some
of them you know she knows those shows
from Nick at night she said but I would
watch them just late night on TV and
that would be like uh everything from
The Honeymooners to uh Carol Bernett
show I used to watch a lot yeah with the
Tim what was his name Tim Conway Conway
Harvey Corman I used to watch that show
uh yeah ton taxi used to watch Mama's
house she used to end every show with
the Q&A with the audience you know they
always have like I'm from Missouri like
she' meet her crowd it's kind of
frightening the worst was when Tracy om
man would do the thing with the crowd at
the end and she'd go oh go home get out
of here go home that stupid voice get
what you doing go home she does a thous
characters and they're all an old weird
English witch like that was my like you
go to school and like you can't wait to
get home to watch some TV like that was
just like and eat like like really bad
food and my mom would make me sandwiches
and you know I was like in like in the
South Park I was like the fat kid I was
just like my mom you know a sandwich and
like uh these kids now like they don't
even need that because they have the
phone so they can like just do it
whenever they want to do it like but we
had to like race home dude racing home
from the bus stop I knew if I got home
at a certain time I could watch two Save
By The Bell
into two Brady bunches M you're
abolutely Isabella if you guys got rid
of cable it wouldn't matter much yeah
really what you watch everything on Hulu
and and Netflix and stuff yeah and
everything's just on demand you it is a
crazy thing to live through and I every
year I get a new technology that I'm
willing to to believe in what is and
like give it to I'm trying to think what
next year's is going to be I didn't
believe in uh onl online payment was a
big one for me but now now I'm okay with
it are you I'm not into that either yeah
you have a flip phone you a flip phone I
don't Uber I don't do any of that stuff
you don't Uber you just all yellow cs I
don't what if you're in what if you're
on the road you need Then I then I guess
I have to walk good man like like chai
Quang K and Kung fol I'm just walking
through the de no when I was out in La I
was just out there and I told this to
Nicki Glazer earlier because we both
were out in La like doing shows and like
uh I took regular cabs it was really
weird to like be the only guy wait like
hailing a cab like I was there to like
Sol the black dollia murder like take me
to Hollywood and Vine don't you
understand the guy that was buying the
first Superman is linked to this murder
and I can prove it goes all the way up
to the studios and those guys those C
drivers are not our C drivers they are
like it's like a small club like you
have to definitely I it definitely
there's some kind of initiation really
it's an Armenian like some kind of like
burn a card with a dob feather like some
kind of weird like and bled out yeah
like if you borrowed a cab driver's car
and showed up they'd be like did you not
do they walk a fire and they don't know
any places outside of their uh Little
World take me to the Melrose improv
improv they like just repeated I'm tell
you that's what I was off I didn't do
Uber for a long time either I stayed
away from that one too and just did cabs
however once you buy the technology it
is way better it is significantly better
because you don't have to say anything
when you get in he's got a map to where
you're going already let's play a game
okay ready let's try and guess how many
people in this room have ridden on an
electric scooter okay okay uh I'm I'll
since I'm it's my game I'll say right
away I have not so you have not okay I
I'm going to say you
have have not really I'm down one not
down one you're up electric scooter I've
never on one no no no never never
absolutely not well here's what
happened who of all the people I I
thought Jay was not yeah you were
waiting for Jay to be like no I was in
San Diego and I saw him lying around all
outside and I where I had to go I walked
it every time but it was like a half
mile or so walk and then I saw them
laying righto they look like they're
kind of fun they do look like they're
kind of fun and so I got the whole app
and loaded it up and they go and then I
got on it and uh you know before I I put
one foot on it and like push the button
to see what it kind of does I'm like oh
yeah look at that it goes then I got on
it and it says you're supposed to kind
of kick a few times and then it'll start
catching I think I was too heavy for it
so it didn't never really caught the
motor part so then I just didn't want to
be embarrassed and get off it with like
an angry
like so I just like foot cranked myself
the whole way there like an idiot yeah I
looked like an just Asian kids
just Cruise like like Tokyo
drifting through everything move analog
yeah I'm sorry everyone I'm too big for
it yeah I have to get the big and tall
before it closes I got a party a big and
tall
scooter when I was in Spokane uh it was
Halloween so right away like everyone's
costumed up but they're also on the
scooters so it's really weird to see and
they're like drunk and they're like
going like no helmets you know just like
dressed up as like The Little Mermaid
going like right into the bar like
wiping out everywhere so I think I think
that's cool I'm sure these guys have all
done
itter no electric scooter what am I I
thought I was H well it's not in New
York really yet no no I know yor it w't
it shouldn't be I really hope they don't
they should do a onetwo punch of like
pot is legal and
scooters
gridlock scooter gridlock I mean
there'll be a thousand scooter deaths a
year if yor impossible when they found
out how to pop the governor off those
things and just take them without using
it I really it is a weird rule then it's
just like you know drop it on the street
wherever you found who gives a
whatever we don't care what are we
nerds we really are designing jobs I
talked to a Uber driver about this the
other day just about the and Dave Smith
used to have a pretty great joke about
he used as being on a desert island but
we always make all the jokes we talk
about on the show a lot our part in the
apocalypse like what it's going to be
after the you know when we're walking
dead life and uh I think we have to
really start making our way to the
Midwest that's what I've decided because
what skills do we forget all the techn
we have no technology we have no
electricity and I feel like we're in a
pile of like web designers and
you know fashion buyers like who's going
to who of us in this build this room
right here is going to kill
skin uh cook like dice up and cook a
deer I couldn't even do the
process of I don't know if I could kill
it yeah that'd be real tough that's
weird because in New York is known for
its chefs but yet we have very few
Hunters that's really going to be tough
we got Gordon Ramsey we got we're all
we're all gatherers no HS guys you know
Fusion food recipes that's great he goes
let me get on the plane I'll give you a
nice Asian fusion deer with it is funny
the people you want as soon as the
goes Haywire the people you're going to
want to be right next to are are wild
Trump supporters right everybody who
everyone says they hate you're going to
want to Buddy up to that guy real quick
cuz he knows how to kill an elk so
people that you called um dumb like you
guys are dumb and they're like I know
how to farm you're
like well Hillary had some good
ideas I just really I I I realized as a
what would 41-year-old I laugh
almost all skill that doesn't involve
technology to survive well did you ever
go camping real camping never no I was
in the Boy Scout so you were you know
was too but I how many badges I would
say I was somewhere I was 10 I was not
really um remember this was like right
after the Vietnam War so being in a
uniform was really tough was really
tough did they call you baby killers I I
was spat on many a Time coming out of an
airport but uh ice cream it was funny
like it was more of like uh get in the
woods kind of scene cuz it was still
like there was no helicopter parenting
it was more like you know okay you guys
you're out there you're camping you know
tang and all that kind of stuff and you
know making fires that you don't need
and just like having good times you know
you wouldn't hear from your parents or
contact them the whole time you were
gone you couldn't not at all like if
something happened to you at boy scout
camp which did happen to me I was hit on
the head with a a log that they would
have to like uh send a runner they would
have to send the fastest that's so funny
skip take this run it down to the the
Fire trail you right I'm pretty sure the
only Boy Scout camping trip I went on
was a setup for a guy to a couple guys
to molest all of us but I just think he
wasn't attracted to me I can only guess
that because we went to in the middle of
the woods I mean an
abandoned we all slept like in an
abandoned house in the middle of the
woods it was to be called a cabin wasn't
fair it was like a place where
crackheads would sleep if this was in a
city it was like a boarded up weird
thing that they put a fire in the
fireplace badass everyone slept on the
floor it was freezing cold like leaves
inside that's not the boy cast and I'm
yeah that's the Caravan part of the
Caravan it was the Blair no I'm telling
you it's what it felt like the whole
vibe was very bizarre and you guys just
went in this old house like I I swear to
you like something like that that's
pretty badass no it's not wow that is
cool no it's not guys it's terrifying
yeah it's terrifying but that's what
makes it so cool look at that you have
fans all over the country so let me tell
you I was in LA right and I had nothing
to do so I went downtown LA they have
this thing called the death Museum you
guys heard of this it's pretty cool it's
got like all the serial killer stuff in
it it's got like just weird like
Polaroids of like just like weird deaths
and like car accidents from like the 60s
and just like all this crazy stuff you
know the guys from the heavens gate that
that cult they bought the bunk beds so
you can like look in at these like
dummies laying in the bunk bed so you
can like and even that's kind of creepy
so that's so Rock and Roll Hall of Fame
it but I said it was kind of like a hot
topic for adults you know it's kind of
like this weird and there all the goth
people in there you know like the goth
kids of LA are in there and I was like
walking around this the old man and I
was like waiting for one of the goth
kids go like do you want to take me home
and do that to me like yeah you're just
looking go I'm just looking at this skin
lamp shade you should have sold IND all
that kind of stuff you should have sold
individual razor blades outside for all
the sad girls hey here you go some of
that you let some of that pressure out
of your thigh you'll feel better the
best part here's a Dixie cup for a grip
they go hey can we get a they have like
my head shot like they just like
downloaded it and they go can you sign
this and I go you got to put it up on
the wall like a dead careers that would
be great like a new Wing put me right
next to Toys are
Us Jeffrey is it very graphic the stuff
they show it yeah it was really it was
more than you thought and it's also like
uh like they had a whole tape of an
autopsy you know like you get to see
like from beginning to end I don't know
who was sitting there and then of course
this you know the CG Allen stuff like
all that kind of stuff in there and uh
they say they have another one in New
Orleans which I assume is more uh that's
all G that's all Gator poies oh you want
to see how a gator ate them man gigantic
Gator head you got to walk into the
bellet to see all the good reptile
deaths yeah all this is Serpentine
related
death everything in here got killed or
is a lizard I tell you what I used to
say that I think I want to see those
things but I really don't too much I'll
tell you what though Bann from TV when I
was spending the night at my friend's
house he put on that tape Bann from TV
and I remember the girl get getting hit
by the train I was like and then
there's the one right after that is uh
in this actually links into the story
what we wanted to bring up for Dave but
in Brazil there was a a hostage
situation and the guy took his stuff off
and tried to act like a hostage and one
of the federales knew it was him and
right when he comes through they just
catch him with a shotgun in the
chest and you see it like yeah you watch
him like slowly go down on he goes down
he's
like also like a student getting shot in
the chest or something and the guy
up the suicide yeah but uh there was
that one it was a
Philadelphia um politician years ago go
that killed himself on live TV after
right but I mean when they have that in
the museum they do yeah but you're but
the the thing is I've actually gotten
almost without even meaning to
desensitized to so much stuff that when
I was I was like I can't the first
beheading I I think a beheading I still
have a hard time with but that first one
that came out the one that everyone saw
Yahoo put it Daniel uh I forget his name
now I feel terrible but not Daniel Pearl
was it yeah Daniel per was a journalist
they when they no he was like a
this guy was like a contractor or
something first one they killed and they
showed the video came out and it was
like you know do not w i w and I really
was one of the only things ever when it
was over I was like I wish I didn't see
that I really but then we watched that
video everyone was getting I felt like a
weirdo we watched the video of the girl
hang out the window of the car like
showing her tits and then like you know
a it hits like a pole it's and I can she
is she beheaded yeah yeah it's gone see
it in the video you can't see it but you
see you you just see like a Ting like
you know her body is like limp and it it
ends right there but I can watch that
now now without like grimacing almost
it's very weird I don't know why you get
desensitized you don't mean to cuz I'm
like it's horrible things yeah yeah but
you like later in the like later when
you go to sleep then then the images
like come into your head like when you
lower your filter that's that's like
where they just like pop in I watch
cartoon when I go into hotel rooms I do
you there it is when you go to uh so she
is she dead yeah yeah okay she dead when
you go to sleep in hotel rooms they
we're in hotel rooms a lot I think Dan
you said you're all lights off TV off
right yeah everything go to bed do you
go to bed everything off um yeah pretty
well it really depends on the room if
it's a suite and I'm not saying that I
rate a suite but sometimes you play
Vegas and they give you like that
conference room area that creeps me out
more than when it's I always go I just
need like a little room I don't need
like that extra like you know I'm going
to have like planed Oceans 11 I don't
know what that is there like I'm having
a peace treaty you know or something you
some other world leaders are getting in
tomorrow at like I'm meeting with the
Legion of Doom or something I went to a
hotel once where they had you like a
weird board like boardroom attached to
the hotel room I remember that that was
a and it's really funny to eat like a
like a Subway sandwich like at this
gigantic table the lonliest boy in the
world look at all this sandwich for none
of my friends but yeah no if I had that
room then I'd have to keep a light on or
two just because I want to know what's
going on I always keep a light on I keep
the TV on with no volume weird I keep a
light on like by the front door of it
the TV with no volume and I watch uh
Cartoon like you know like the family gu
type cartoons on my computer what would
happen if you turn all night long like
you just need that all night long just
to keep you from when I fall asleep
eventually the computer will just like
it kind of does that like are you still
watching this acknowledge it so I don't
care when that happens but if I wake up
for five minutes if not even see if I
just wake up and open my eyes and I see
that it's that screen like continue
watching or leave it off I always hit
continue and it comes back on I go back
to sleep yeah wow Christine had to learn
uh to sleep with you were a sleep in the
dark person she had to learn to sleep so
even at home you have to keep a light on
not a light TV though you keep the TV on
while you sleep the entire time of night
it goes off eventually you know that's
like really bad for you I feel like I'm
fine yeah they're saying like for your
sleep cycle it's really bad to sleep in
they think it's bad am I going to watch
hellrazer judgment yeah oh well that's
the thing yeah I can only watch horror
movies late and Christine falls asleep
and for whatever reason her sleeping
presence is the only thing that will
save me from Monsters okay so you're
very powerful in your sleep it's I'm
telling you it's very weird I would
never watch a horror movie late night on
the road I never it wigs me out I get
that fear sometimes I walk a little fast
getting out of the elevator like a Club
Quarters Hotel in San Fram where you
stay how was like windy hallways that's
ter something like that when you get off
in shining it's just quiet and and empty
and you're just walking you just hear
all you hear is your footsteps and your
bag swinging or whatever and it's uh and
you're like this is haunted it has to be
look at thisall I get very wigged out
and then the ice machine goes you're
like but I Pissed My Pants and started
crying switch rooms cuz it was haunted
dude straight up I've been in a haunted
room too Vancouver the you has to move
oh absolutely yeah I've I've I've the
room in the comedy mix I don't know what
it was I was trying to go to bed and I
was lying there and I just it sounded
like a pipe was Dripping and then I
walked and then the the noise moved and
it was with me and I called
downstairs I was like can I move I I I'm
hearing something can I move and they're
like yeah sure of course and then I
moved rooms and slept great and then did
they tell you it was haunted no I never
found that out kind of just ran I know I
bet you there's a lot of like people who
were into that who would want to stay in
the room cuz it's haunted that's really
weird to me when people are like yeah no
let's go to this haunted house and stay
you pay like 600 bucks the place some
lady got raped and murder downstairs
like I'm good that's like a that's like
a weird people travel around to like
these these sites you know yeah that's a
weird would you take a great deal on an
apartment if like a junkie died there no
no I I've actually like had had like
Apartments where people did die and all
that kind of stuff and they just now
have to tell you like that's part of it
like they have to tell you the record
but does it matter to you if it's
someone just died in their bed of old
age or heart attack F you're okay with
that but if a murder you wouldn't I
would rather it be someone cooler than
an old age person yeah yeah if think go
this guy died getting his dick sucked
and doing crack and heroin i' be
like that would be good that's a badass
if he's haunting me that guy's a party
can I sleep in
[Music]
sunglasses
ow